You know, you're late, Tommy
你知道，你硗砹耍米
Rico, relax
波多黎各，放
Okay, then, okay, you're the boss, come on
那好吧，好吧，你是老，戆
That's Hugo Porto's mob, huh?
@是雨果波D的暴徒，是吧？
He tried to move in on Big Sep's territory down in Atlantic City
他D进入大西洋城
Killed Victor Viking's mom in the process
S克多海I⒑Φ在@^程中
Wow, what a bunch of scumbags, huh?
哇，@N一堆scumbags，是吧？
Whatever, and there's proof for Big Sep, you got a ticket on the red-eye
不管Y果如何，而且也C明了，你有t眼C票
The heads are nice and clean and ready to go, okay?
人很不e，乾Q，浜昧耍好幔
Okay
好
Tommy, Big Sep's hot
米，
I'm two weeks late delivering the meat
我蛇L後提供的
If he doesn't get that by noon tomorrow, more heads are gonna roll
如果他]有得到，到明天中午，推出更多的
- You know what I mean? - No problem
- 你知道我是什N意思？ - ]}
Do you love me?
你畚幔
- Where you headed? San Diego? - Mexico
- 你要去哪海柯}地哥？ - 墨西哥
- You have a good flight - Thanks a lot
- 你有一良好的w行 - 非常感x
Do you love me? Do you love me?
你畚幔磕畚幔
How you doing?
你怎N樱
Thank you, thanks
xx你，xx
Step over here please
在@e步
Gun! She's got a gun!
！她有！
I don't even own a gun!
我什至不碛凶约旱！
- Hey, kid, is this yours? - Yeah
- 嘿，孩子，@是你的幔 - 是啊
Do me a favor, will you? Put that right under the seat
臀乙忙，好幔堪堰@N嗬座位下
And see maybe if you can keep that right near you
然後看看也S如果你能保持@N嗬靠近你
I got some important stuff in this bag
我得到了一些重要的|西在@袋子
I'd like to keep it close by me, you know what I mean?
我想保持它P]我，你知道我是什N意思？
Thanks, that's really nice of you
xx，真的xx你
- Good kid, thank you - Okay
- 好孩子，xx你 - 好
Atta boy, fits right under there
好小子，m合在有嗬
No, it doesn't fit right under there
不，它不m合下有嗬
Maybe you can get a spot in another bin, thanks, I appreciate that
也S你可以得到一c在另一斌，xx，我明白
It's nice of you
它xx你
Excuse me
Σ黄
Careful, careful
小心，小心
I almost didn't make it
我缀]有成功
Well, I'm sure that someone is glad you did
嗯，我敢肯定，有人很高d你]有
Let's see, 49C, right down this way
我看看，49c及，一直@
Thanks
xx
- Excuse me, sir, is this yours? - Yeah
- Σ黄穑先生，@是你的幔 - 是啊
I'm sorry, we'll need to use this compartment
Σ黄穑我需要使用@
Would you mind using another one?
你介意使用e的？
Because I have valuable family heirlooms in there
因槲矣F的骷在那e
Sir, as you can plainly see, this is an emergency situation
主席先生，你可以清楚地看到，@是一o急情r
Well, maybe you can use somebody else's bin
嗯，也S你可以使用e人的bin
I mean, this kid's not using all of his
我的意思是，@孩子不是他的使用所有
Would you mind if they used some of yours?
你不介意，他用了一些你的？
Hey, excuse me, but screw you
嘿，Σ黄穑你螺
Hey, hey, come on, be nice, be a gentleman, will you?
嘿，嘿，戆桑做好青年，是一士，你意幔
We're trying to help over here, here, let me help you
我正在努力椭在@e，在@e，我湍
This goes right over here, it's small
@正好就在@e，它的小
That's okay, thanks, don't... don't?
]PS，xx，不要...]有？
Wait! Wait! Don't kick it!
等待！等待！不要踢了！
For God's sake, those are live human organs!
看在上帝的份上，@些都是活的人w器官！
Trust me, pal, they don't feel it
相信我，伙，他不X得
Would you sit down please?
你坐下砗幔
Sir, I'm really sorry about that
主席先生，我真的很抱歉，
- Sir, we're gonna have to use your bin - Excuse me? but?
- 主席先生，我得使用您斌 - Σ黄鹞幔康是？
And actually, sir, I think your bag is over the size limit
而H上，先生，我X得你的包超^大小限制
Well, no, because see, the guy outside measured this and he said that it was okay
哦，不，因榭吹降模@砘y量外，他f@是好的
Sir, it's clearly over the size limit, it will have to go in cargo
主席先生，@@然超^大小限制，它必走物
Listen, wait a minute, wait a minute?
著，等一下，等一下？
Hold on, hold on a second, listen
等一下，等一下，
Maybe we could just leave my bag where it is, all right?
也S我可以只o我的包在哪海好幔
Are you trying to bribe me, sir?
你是不是想VT我，先生？
No. I'm trying to purchase a place for my bag, which I already...
不，我想I一我的提包，我已 ...
The place for your bag is in cargo, sir
@地方δ愕陌是在物，先生
Excuse me, maybe I'll just take another flight
Σ黄穑或S我袢×硪环Nw行
Fine, the next flight to San Diego leaves in seven hours, sir
P款，下次w行到圣迭戈~七小r，先生
All right, let me make a phone call
好吧，我打
Sir, do you actually think that we're gonna hold the plane while you use the phone
主席先生，你真的J椋我要保持wC的同r使用手C
Now, are you flying with us tonight or not?
F在，你乘坐我的班C今晚或]有？
- All right, Miss Burke? - Yes
- 好吧，小姐伯克？ - 是
- That's your name, right?
- @就是你的名字，ΣΓ
This bag better be in San Diego, you'll be in a lot of trouble if it's not
@包最好是在}地哥，你在很多的麻，如果它不是
Yes, sir, it will be the very first off the plane
是的，先生，@⑹窍嘛wC的第一
Does that make you happy?
@是否你幸福幔
- When it's there, then I'll be happy - Okay
- 它的存在，那N我很高d - 好
Have a seat, sir, thank you
坐，先生，xx你
Happy? Yeah, I'm happy, I'm thrilled
快罚渴前。我很高d，我很高d
Happy
快
What are you looking at?
你在看什N？
You started all this with those friggin' organs
你_始@一切c@些受{咒的器官
You're happy, right? Happy, who's happy?
你是幸福的，ΣΓ靠罚l的幸福幔
Look, I think we got off on the wrong foot, I'm Charlie
你看，我J槲下了在e`的_，我查
So, where you headed?
所以，你要去哪海
I'm gonna meet my girlfriend's parents
我要我的女朋友的父母
She races these cars
她@些比
She's great, she's great!
她是ゴ蟮模她的ゴ螅
I wish her parents thought the same of me, I'm on my way to meet them for the first time
我想她的父母J橥拥奈叶言，我ξ业姆绞剑以M足他的第一次
I haven't seen her in like six months, and...
我]有看到^她像六月，K且 ...
Yeah, well, I'm gonna go to sleep
是啊，我要去睡X
Think about what you're gonna say to them, okay?
想想你跟他f，好幔
Yeah, I don't know, because I mean I haven't even met them
是啊，我不知道，因槲业囊馑际俏疫]有^他
Already the father, he doesn't like me, I know
已是父H，他不喜g我，我知道
I could understand that, I just met you and I don't like you either
我能理解，我JR你，我不喜g你要么
I got to sleep, didn't you hear me? Come on
我得睡X，]有你了幔戆
I'm just trying to make conversation, but...
我只是想和她聊聊，可是...
Good, make it in sign language
好，使之在手Z
Laurie?
谘e？
- Something wrong? - No
- 怎N了？ - o
- You look great - Thanks
- 你看起砗馨 - xx
- What is the matter? - Nothing, let's talk about it later
- 什N是怎N回事？ - ]什N，我碚以後
Okay
好
Oh, no. No, Jesus, please, no!
哦，不。不，耶d，，不！
Charlie Pritchett! Shit!
查理普里奇特！的！
What do you have in there? It looks like you packed for a month
你有什N在那e？它看起硐衲阊b了一月
You know me, ready for anything
你了解我，涫颤N
- Oh, boy, look at this loser - Honey! Be nice now, come on
- 哦，孩子，看看@失≌ - H鄣模‖F在是好的，戆
Charlie, these are my parents, Annette and Dick
查理，@是我的父母，涡闵和迪克
- Annette - Charlie, it's a real pleasure
- 涡闵 - 查理，@是一真正的快
Dick, very nice to meet you, this is for you
迪克，很高dJR你，@是槟
Oh, these wrappings are beautiful, thank you
哦，@些包b很漂亮，xx你
Oh, my God! Dick, I left yours on the plane...
噢，我的上帝！迪克，我x_你的wC上...
No, no, no, why don't you call the airlines?
不，不，不，你槭颤N不叫航空公司幔
We got a long ride, we've got to make tracks
我有很L的程，我不得不做出曲目
Sorry
Σ黄
Woodgy, why don't you ride shotgun with your dad?
Woodgy，你槭颤N不TB和你爸爸？
Wudji? Wudji like me to drive?
Wudji？ Wudji像我@娱_幔
I think I can handle it
我想我能付自如
No... no... Jesus
第..不...耶d
House of pain
h院疼痛
- Yeah, hello, who's this? - This is Qaddafi, who's this?
- 是啊，你好，l的呢？ - @是卡扎菲，l的呢？
Qaddafi, huh? Listen, this is Bill, I'm an old friend of Charlie Pritchett's
卡扎菲，是吧？著，@是比，我的老朋友查理Pritchett的
I was wondering if you could help me find him
我想知道你能不能臀艺业剿
Yeah, he's gone on spring break with the rest of America
是啊，他走在春假，其N的美
- Did you try looking in Mexico? - That's very funny
- 看你有]有L在墨西哥？ - @是非常可笑
Look, this is really important
看，@是非常重要的
You think you could be a little more specific, Qaddafi?
你以槟隳芨具w一c，卡扎菲？
Not unless it's for a grade
不，除非它是榱顺煽
Hey, Bill, is it? Tell me if this sounds like a phone hanging up
嘿，比，是幔扛嬖V我，如果@起硐褚
Yeah! Shit! Shit!
是啊！的！的！
I need a flight to Bethesda University
我需要一航班塞斯_大W
I'm not sure the University has their own airport
我不知道大W都有自己的C
But we can fly you to Baltimore, will that do?
但是我可以您到巴的摩，能行幔
Hey, don't get cute with me, asshole, huh?
嘿，不要可鄣奈遥混蛋，是吧？
Wake up, people, we're here! Made it in record time
醒醒吧，人，我在@e！它在最短的rgu造
- I'm famished - Oh, me too
- 我I - 哦，我也是
Boy, could I use a Margarita, what time is it?
好砘铮我可以用一格塔，F在是什Nr候？
Thirteen fifty hours
十三五十小r
Bear, remember what we agreed about your drinking?
熊，得我同意你喝酒幔
You be a good bear, take one of your new pills
你是一很好的承，袢∧的一新的丸
They make me woozy, Wooly
他使我^昏眼花，毛茸茸
Besides, I said I could use a drink, I didn't say I'm having one
此外，我f我可以用一喝，我K]有f我有一
Listen, there is absolutely nothing in this whole world
著，^]有在@整世界
That could ever, ever make me take a drink again
@可能永h，永h我喝一口再
So, relax, okay?
所以，放，好幔
- Bienvenidos! Welcome back, senior - Hola, Juan
- Bienvenidos！g迎回恚高 - HOLA的，胡安
Hope you catch some big ones this time
希望你抓住一些大的@r候
Gracias, gracias
格拉西斯，格拉西斯
- Manny, I ran into a little delay here - What do you mean, a delay?
- 曼尼，我遇到了一小的延t在@e - 你是什N意思，延t？
Excuse me, are you going to be long?
Σ黄穑你要L幔
- A day, maybe two - On the phone?
- 一天，也S是 - 在手C上？
What? What the hell's happened, Tommy?
什N？什N是地z的l生，米？
Manny, I can't go into it right now but it's going to be okay
曼尼，我不能M入它的嗬，但F在它都好起淼
All right? I mean, can't you talk to Big Sep?
好吧？我的意思是，你能不能跟大九月？
Big Sep is riding me like a race horse, I told you if it was late...
大月是T我X得像一匹R，我告V你，如果天色已晚...
Listen, the job is finished, so what's the big deal with the delivery?
，作I完成，所以有什N大不了的交？
Tommy, you didn't lose nothing, did you?
米，你]有失去什N，是幔
Manny, you know how many years I did this for your father?
曼尼，你知道多年恚我@幼瞿愕母赣H幔
How could you even ask me something like that?
你怎N那N我似的|西？
Mister?
先生？
Hey, lady, you interrupt me one more time, you're gonna swallow this phone
嘿，小姐，你打辔乙淮危你吞下@
Now get out of here
F在x_@e
Go ahead, take it on the heels
戆桑把它的高跟鞋
One day, you got one day, Tommy
有一天，你有一天，米
If big Sep doesn't get those heads in his hands by noon tomorrow
如果]有得到大九月的^在他手中明天中午前
You might as well chop off your own head and put it in with the others, capish?
你不如砍掉自己的^，把它c其他的，capish？
Don't worry about it, all right? He'll have them before they start stinking
e心，]事吧？他⒆他才_始l臭
- Please or you'll be stinking - Yeah, yeah, I know what you mean
- 否t你臭 - 是啊，是啊，我知道你是什N意思
- About time - Yeah, I know
- P於rg - 是啊，我知道
Here, it's all yours
在@e，@一切都凫赌
We've done a lot of redecorating since you've been here, senor
我已做了很多的b修，因槟阋恢痹谶@e，先生
It's quite lovely, we hope you enjoy it
@是相可鄣模我希望你喜g
- It's beautiful - Senor Pritchett... your room
- @是美的 - 塞{普里奇特...你的房g
Thank you
xx
The mini-bar, el bano, the bathroom
迷你酒吧，蟀椭Z，l生g
If you need anything, please call me
如果你需要什N，o我打
Everybody unpack later
大家解横
They're only serving lunch downstairs for ten more minutes
他只供午餐下鞘分
- Yes sir, no problem - Good
- 是的，先生，]} - 好
Pepe, venga! Pepe, venga!
佩佩，venga！佩佩，venga！
- Come on, Bear - I'm coming, Wooly
- 戆桑熊 - 我砹耍毛茸茸
It's 206, room 206
@是206 206室
Okay, Laurie, what's going on?
好吧，谘e，@是怎N回事？
Not now, let' just talk about it later, okay?
F在不行，我只是以後，好幔
No, let's talk about it now
不，我F在它
Look, Charlie, I don't know quite how to put this
你看，查理，我不知道怎N把@
But... I think I want a divorce
但是...我想我要x婚
What? A divorce? We're not even married, we're not even engaged
什N？x婚幔课甚至不Y婚，我甚至不氖
You know what I mean
你知道我是什N意思
That's why you invited me here? To tell me this?
@就是槭颤N你邀我磉@e？告V我@？
I thought you invited me to meet your parents
我以槟阏我去你的父母
I didn't really actually invite you
其我K]有真正邀您
Excuse me, but you invited me to your parents' house
Σ黄穑但你邀我去你父母家
And then you called and said we were coming to Mexico instead
然後你打黼，f我是砟西哥，而不是
When I said we were going to Mexico, I didn't actually mean you
我f我去墨西哥，我其]有f你
What?!
什N？！
It was just supposed to be me and my parents for my dad's birthday
@只是是我和我的父母槲野职值纳日
And you got so excited; I didn't know how to break it to you
而你有@N激樱我不知道如何打破它o你
Laurie, what's happened to you?
谘e，有什N事幔
Six months at home and you've mutated
六月回家，你已突
From a fun-loving free spirit into... Nancy Reagan
囊有趣的酆米杂傻木神之中...南希e根
Look, I just want stability in my life, Charlie
你看，我只是想在我的生活定，查理
I need to be with someone who really knows who they are
我需要ce人l真正知道他是l
And knows what they want in life
K知道他想要的|西在生活中
You know what this is all about? Your folks
你知道@是怎N一回事？你父母
They don't like me, and it's affecting the way that you feel about me
他不喜g我，它的影的方式，你ξ业目捶
But just wait, Laurie
但是，只是等待，邴
My being here will turn out to be a blessing in disguise
我被@e⒆成一因得福
I'm not giving up on you, Laurie
我不放你，邴
- Is my hair all right? - I am open-minded
- 我的^好幔 - 我很_明
It's just that he's such a dip!
只是，他的@N下降！
Do you think he's a dip? I think he's really cute
你J樗是一浸？我J樗真的很可
And he seems funny, and he seems smart
他似乎很有趣，他似乎明
I mean, what do you want for Laurie?
我的意思是，你怎N想的谘e？
I want what I was when I was his age
我想我是我是他的年g
- I was charismatic, ambitious... - That's right
- 我是有魅力，有野心... - @是正_的
- I was clearly headed to the top - Clearly, darling
- 我清楚地前往 - @然，H鄣
The very, very top
非常，非常部
I mean, we can be honest with each other when we're alone, can't we?
我的意思是，我可以互相f，我，我不能？
Oh, I think that's a good idea, Wooly
哦，我想@是一好主意，毛茸茸
I've always wanted to be...
我一直想成 ...
Oh, I forgot something, will you go down and get us a table?
哦，我忘了的|西，你就下恚我一桌子幔
- What's the problem? - No problem, no problem
- 有什N}幔 - ]}，]}
I just forgot something and I'll be there in just a second
我就忘了的|西，我在那e，在短短一秒
Okay? I'm running
好幔课疫\行
Senorita, no, no, it's for decoration, not for sale, sorry
Senorita，不，不，它是檠b，不u的，Σ黄
I better go check on Bear
我得去z查熊
- Ah, Mrs. Bennett - There you are, Bear
- 啊，忍胤蛉 - 你砹耍熊
We ordered you an enchilada
我叫你一拉_
- Bear, are you all right? - Mrs. Bennett?
- 熊，你]事吧？ - 忍靥太？
Jesus! Ma, are you okay?
耶d！R，你]事吧？
- Would you, would you like to... to sit? - Mom, what are you doing?
- 你，你想...坐？ - ，你在质颤N？
Good God, Bear, don't tell me you've been drinking again
天哪，熊，不要告V我你一直在喝了
Now, remember what the doctor said, take nice deep breaths
F在，得t生f，袢∩詈粑好
- I have some pills if you're not feeling well - Yeah, why don't you take some?
- 我有一些片，如果你不舒服 - 是啊，你槭颤N不袢∫恍？
It's, it's, it's... all right, folks
它的，它的，它的...好吧，伙
She's just a little hungry, she's hungry and her blood sugar's dropped
她只是有cI了，她I了，她的血糖的下降
Are you hungry, Bear?
你I了，熊？
- Mom, for God's sake? - Would you like an enchilada?
- ，偏偏？ - 你想一拉_？
It's all right, folks! No harm done
]事了，lH！o妨
They're just happy to see each other
他只是很高d地看到Ψ
You little son of a bitch, I should have known
你@小狗娘B的，我知道
Wake up, Qaddafi, we're gonna play College Bowl
醒醒吧，卡扎菲，我要在大W打碗
For ten points of your life...
十c你的生活...
Hey Stevie, you got any notes from last night? I don't need them
嘿，杰拉德，你有]有注意到，昨天晚上？我K不需要它
Hey!
嘿！
No, no, I've got it, thank you very much
不，不，我已知道了，非常感x你
Seniorita, your mother is going to be fine
Seniorita，你母H是要被P款
Take this please
藉此
Senor, I gave her a sedative, it's muy, muy strong
塞{，我o了她一o，它的muy，muy
- Let her rest, huh? - Thank you, doctor
- 她休息吧？ - xx你，t生
We've only been back here an hour and already she's on the booze
我才回到@e一小r，她已P於酒
Would you go easy on her, dad? She's obviously under a lot of stress
你去容易在她身上，爸爸？她@然下了不少的毫
Okay
好
When she wakes up, we won't mention a thing, okay, Laurie?
她醒r，我⒉惶岬氖拢]PS，谘e？
Why don't you watch her, while Charlie and I go rent a boat for tomorrow?
槭颤N你不看她，而查理和我去租了一l船明天？
- Okay, Charlie? - Yeah, great
- 好吧，查理？ - 是啊，大
Is my hair okay?
我的^好幔
Uh, do, do you mind if l change my shirt before we go?
嗯，做什N，你不介意升改了我的r衫，然後才去？
No, I'll use the phone in your room so I don't disturb her
不，我用手C在你的房g，所以我不打_她
All right, we're gonna play a game called Be Honest With Me?
好吧，我要玩一[蚪姓\我幔
Now, the rules are very simple
F在，t很
l ask you a question and you have to be honest with me, okay?
升你一}，你必要\的和我，好幔
Now, where did Charlie Pritchett go on vacation?
F在，查理普里奇特哪喝ザ燃伲
Second rule, you have to answer, Qaddafi
第二lt，你必回答，卡扎菲
- Why does he keep calling you Qaddafi? - I don't know
- 槭颤N他o你打卡扎菲？ - 我不知道
Now, look, I don't want to have to put you kids through hell
F在，你看，我不想你的孩子必通^地z
So let me tell you what's going to happen here
因此，我砀嬖V你@是怎N回事，就l生在@e
First, I'm gonna hurt you, then you're gonna try to be brave
首先，我要害你，那N你逞
Then I'm gonna hurt you again, and you're gonna tell me everything
然後我再次害你，你是要告V我的一切
That's not being honest, that's not honest
@不是\，@是不老
That's not honest!
@是不老！
Now, look, this is not gonna get any easier, it's only gonna get harder
F在看，@是不得到任何容易，它只是越碓诫y
So, I don't know why you're protecting this kid, because I'm gonna find him
所以，我不知道你槭颤N保o@孩子，因槲乙找到他
There we go, atta boy
我走吧，好小子
l swear to God, we don't know where he is all he said was Mexico and he's ...
升向上帝l誓，我不知道他在哪ef的是墨西哥和他的...
Come on!
戆桑
We're not trying to protect him!
我不是要保o他！
I'm not going to repeat myself!
我不想重}我自己！
Mom, if you want to come down, you're certainly welcome
，如果你要砹耍你然g迎
It's just that the weather is terrible
@只是很可怕的天
Well, it's rained since we got here, mom, there are storms everywhere
嗯，@是下雨，因槲淼竭@e，，有L暴o不在
l mean more storms are on the way
我的意思是多L浪的道路上
Mom, I'm just thinking about you
，我只是想你
Mom, l... we..., of course we'd love to have your company, mom
，湖..我 ...，我然希望有你的公司，
Well, I know you're young enough to travel, it has nothing to do with that
嗯，我知道你年p，能蚵眯校它]有任何c做
Mom... mom, please, please, mom, please don't dredge that up
...，，，，不要疏通，截至
What's the matter? Are you okay?
什N事？你]事吧？
l, uh, uh, ants, ants everywhere
升，嗯，嗯，，o不在
Ants' I don't see any ants, what are you talking about?
'我]有看到任何，你f什N？
Mom, there are ants down here, ants everywhere
，@河形，o不在
Mom, please don't dredge that up
，不要疏通，截至
Because it's got nothing to do with her
因樗有c她oP
What is it? What is it?
是什N呢？是什N呢？
- I have a cramp in my leg - A cramp?
- 我有我的腿抽筋 - 抽筋？
Ay, ah!
是啊，啊！
Well, pull yourself together, stop screaming
好吧，振作起恚停止尖叫
I'm, I'm sorry, I'm...
我，Σ黄穑我...
No, mom, I'm not arguing with my wife, I'm arguing with you
不，，我K不J槲业钠拮樱我c你q
l mean, mom, mom, please, I'll have to call you back
我的意思是，，，，我得o你回
Mom, I'll call you back, I'll call you right back
，我o你回，我打o你身
Can you keep it down?
你能保持下幔
Now, why don't I meet you downstairs in the lobby in say, five minutes?
那N，槭颤N不我和你在窍麓d中f，五分？
- Five minutes? - All right?
- 五分？ - 所有的嗬？
Five minutos!
五minutos！
And don't send this laundry out, it's gonna cost me an arm and a leg!
，也不要把@洗衣房出恚它的成本要我一b胳膊和一l腿！
yeah!
是啊！
Oh, yeah! Obviously, this is, this isn't real
哦，是啊！@然，@是，@不是真
It's a, it's, it's a fake, it's a fake
@是一，它的，它是假的，@是一假的
God! God!
神！神！
Senor! Senor!
塞{！塞{！
- Are you okay? - I am fine
- 你好幔 - 我很好
l just, I ate a hot pepper
升只是，我吃了辣椒
- Oh, ah, hot pepper - Venga, Pepe
- 哦，啊，辣椒 - Venga，佩佩
No, no, no
不，不，不
Charlie, are you okay?
查理，你]事吧？
I'm fine, I just ate a killer pepper
我很好，我只是吃了辣椒⑹
A chili pepper, I'm fine
一辣椒，我]事
There's some water in the mini-bar, senor
有一些水在迷你酒吧，塞{
No, no, no l like the sensation
不，不，不一拥母杏X升
I' yee haw! Yee haw!
我哼筮螅∽h山楂！
Enchilada!
拉_！
Okay, well you call me if you need anything, eh?
好吧，那N你叫我，如果你需要什N，是幔
- Will do, thank you, Paco - Pepe, venga!
- 我的，xx你，柏高 - 佩佩，venga！
Pepe, come on! Pepe!
佩佩，戆桑∨迮澹
- God! - Charlie, what's going on?
- 上帝！ - 查理，@是怎N回事？
The police, this has got to be a setup! Oh, God!
警方，@⑹且O置！哦，上帝！
There's got to be a camera or something
我有了一相C或|西
We're in Mexico, why would there be a camera in Mexico?
我在墨西哥，槭颤N有一z像^在墨西哥？
Mexican Candid Camera, still on the air!
墨西哥偷拍，仍然在空猓
Charlie! You're acting insane!
查理！你表F太狂了！
- I'm okay - Would you get it together?
- 我好 - 你得到它在一起幔
- Okay? - I'm okay
- 好吧？ - 我]事
What the hell is going on?
@到底是怎N回事？
Look, Laurie, you gotta promise you won't freak, okay?
你看，谘e，你必保C你不怪胎，好幔
Okay
好
I found something in my duffel bag
我找到了我的行李袋
Something, oh... I mean, look, it's a...
|西哦...我的意思是，你看，它的答..
- What? - Forget it, it's nothing, it's nothing
- 什N？ - 算了，]什N，]什N
- Charlie Pritchett, you're such a sneak - No!
- 查理普里奇特，你真是一行 - 不！
You got me a present, I didn't know you got me one
你我一Y物，我不知道你有我一
No! No! It's not a present Laurie!
不！不！@不是一本谘e！
Laurie, don't open it, it's a head
谘e，不要打_它，它的^
Laurie
谘e
Laurie!
谘e！
Are you okay? Honey, are you all right?
你]事吧？H鄣模你]事吧？
Yeah
是啊
- Senora, are you all right? - She's fine, everything's fine
- 塞Z拉，你]事吧？ - 她很好，一切都很好
She had a pepper too, she loves them, actually, she'll be fine
她有一辣椒太多，她鬯，其，她]事的
Are you sure, senorita?
你_定，senorita？
Pepe, Pepe, venga
佩佩，佩佩，venga
Pepe, venga!
佩佩，venga！
Pepe!
佩佩！
Pepe, andale! Vamos
佩佩，安_R！瓦莫斯
You call me if you need anything, eh?
你叫我，如果你需要什N，是幔
Will do, thank you, Paco, bye-bye
我的，xx你，柏高，再，再
All right
所有嗬
Laurie, are you okay? Can you stop screaming?
谘e，你]事吧？你能停止尖叫？
Good God, Charlie, what are you doing with a head in your bag?
天哪，查理，你在做什N用的^在你的包？
I don't know, you think I know?
我不知道，你X得我怎N知道？
Yes, I think you'd know If I had a head in my bag, I think I'd know
是的，我想你就知道，如果我有一^在我的包，我想我知道
Laurie, Laurie, don't get upset but there's more than one
谘e，谘e，不要不高d，但有一以上的
What? Charlie, there's two?
什N？查理，有？
- No - Three? Four? How many?
- ]有 - 三？四？有多少？
Eight?
八？
It's those gringos, son locos
它的那些gringos，鹤C
Laurie, you're not in the hall, you're in the closet
谘e，你不是在大de，你在衣e
Don't you think I realize that?
y道你不X得我知道幔
- Laurie - I'm not coming out
- 谘e - 我不出
- Laurie! - I'm not!
- 谘e！ - 我不是！
- You have to come out! - No!
- 你要砹耍 - 不！
The bodies are in there
@些企w都是在那e
I was... I was kidding, I was kidding
我是...我是_玩笑，我是在_玩笑
Kidding? You're kidding at a time like this?
_玩笑吧？你在_玩笑一次@幔
Well, I had to calm you down
嗯，我o你平o下砹
For God's sake, Laurie, try to stay calm, okay?
看在上帝的份上，谘e，M量保持冷o，好幔
Calm? You expect me to remain calm
冷o？你以槲保持冷o
When you have eight human heads in your luggage?
你有8人的^在你的行李幔
Laurie, there may be two people in China who didn't hear you
谘e，可能有人在中l]有到你
- Then what the hell is going on? - I wish I knew
- 那N@到底是怎N回事？ - 我希望我能知道
Could it be Steve or Ernie playing some sort of sick, hideous, medical prank?
y道是史蒂夫或恩尼玩某N病B，h陋，t鹤。
I don't think so, the thought of blood bothers Steve
我不@NJ椋本以槔_史蒂夫血
And this isn't Ernie's style
@是不是厄尼的L格
They're my best friends, but come on, they're dull guys with dull lives
他是我最好的朋友，但拜，他是平淡乏味的生活c人
You psycho! You psycho!
你心理！你心理！
We don't know anything!
我不知道！
I don't know shit!
我不知道狗屎！
You're right
你f得
Besides, the only heads we have access to are cadavers
此外，唯一的元首，我能颢@得的企w
- And these heads are fresh - Charlie!
- @些都是新r的^ - 查理！
I'm sorry, but it's true, check it out for yourself
Σ黄穑但@是事，z查出樽约
No!
不！
- Let's call the police - No! No! No!
- 我叫警察了 - 不！不！不！
- Why? - Because we're in Mexico, Laurie
- 槭颤N？ - 因槲是在墨西哥，邴
A third world country. You don't just call the police in a third world country
第三世界家。你不只是叫警察在一第三世界家
And tell them you found eight human heads in your luggage
K告V他你lF八人^在你的行李
- Why not? - Because they have no laws here!
- 槭颤N不呢？ - 因樗]有法律在@e！
- They'll turn me into a taco! - All right, what do you suggest then?
- 他把我成橐塔科！ - 好吧，你有什N建h呢？
We have to think this thing through rationally
我要通^合理J檫@事
- Okay? - Oh, my God, Charlie
- 好吧？ - 哦，我的上帝，查理
- What if they have your bag? - What?
- 如果他有你的包幔 - 什N？
Your bag! What if the person who owns this bag has your bag?
你的包！如果那人l碛羞@包包，你的包幔
They're going to come looking for you
他碚夷
Laurie, I just took a mental inventory of my bag
谘e，我只是把我的精神袋齑
There's no... there's nothing in that bag that could possibly lead them here
有]有 ...有]有在@袋子有可能е滤在@e
His family lives in Clarion, Vermont! They're in the furniture business
他的家人住在歌罚佛蒙特！他在家具I
Laurie is from Denver! Last name, Bennett
谘e是牡し穑⌒帐希班尼特
B-e-n-n-e-t-t!
忍兀
On vacation in Mexico
在墨西哥度假
Okay, that's reassuring What do we do?
好吧，@是令人欣慰我怎Nk？
Simple! All we have to do is throw them away
危∥所要做的就是把它扔掉
They lock the garbage
他i定的垃圾
Senor Pritchett?
塞{普里奇特？
- Ah, Paco - Can I help you?
- 啊，帕 - 我可以湍幔
No, no, I was just putting the, the, the trash in the garbage
不，不，我只是把在中，，垃圾中的垃圾
Putting the garbage in the trash, you know?
把垃圾中的垃圾，你知道幔
- I'll take it for you - No, no, I got it
- 我要δ - 不，不，我知道了
- What is it? - It's? it's none of your business
- 是什N？ - @是？@c你oP
No, Senor, I meant what kind of garbage is it? Aluminum? Plastic?
不，先生，我的意思是什N拥睦圾是什N？X？塑料？
We recycle here
在@e我回收
It's, it's really not recyclable, it's, it's perishable
@是，@真的不能回收利用，它的，它的易腐
- Oh, well, perishables we compost - It's really not compostable
- 哦，好，易腐我堆肥 - @是真的不是堆肥
Sure it is! Everything perishable is compostable
然它是！一切易腐是堆肥
Jesus Christ!
耶d基督！
I mean, come on!
我的意思是，加油！
I'm sorry, senor! Go ahead and put it in
Σ黄穑先生！戆桑把它放在
- Thank you - I'll take care of it later
- xx你 - 我照它的後面
Actually, you know what? It's fine I'll just take it back
其，你知道幔窟@P款我只是把它收回
It's really not that bad. I just need some oil and formaldehyde and vinegar
@真的]有那N糟。我只是需要一些油，甲醛和醋
And it'll be just as good as...
而@⑹且雍...
- Are you sure, senor? - Yes, thank you, Paco
- 您是否肯定，先生？ - 是的，xx你，帕
Mom, why are you bringing my inheritance into this?
，你槭颤N我到@^承？
Excuse me!
Σ黄穑
You still haven't changed? What are you doing?
您]有改？你在质颤N？
- Well, l... - No, not you, mom
- 嗯，湖.. - 不，不是你，
I found a roa... roa... a rat in my room
我lF了一居留 ...居留 ...老鼠在我的房g
And it had a ball of...
而且它有一球...
I don't wanna be rude, but are you coming?
我不想oY，但你幔
Or am I going to spend the entire day waiting in the lobby for you?
或者我花一整天在大堂等你幔
I am so sorry, I'll be right down
我很抱歉，我R上就下
What am I going to do? Flush them?
我怎Nk？_洗呢？
Nothing fits around here
在@e]有m合
No, no, no, por favor , no clean
不，不，不，健波成，]有乾Q的
No clean, room clean, no clean
]有乾Q，房g乾Q，]有乾Q的
- No clean - No clean, gracias
- ]有乾Q的 - 不乾Q，格拉西斯
No, I mean, I'm, I'm asking you to come, mom
不，我的意思是，我，我要求你恚
But there's really no need for you to come Mom, it's two hundred degrees here
但在]有必要你，它的二百度在@e
You go in here! Like that!
在@e你去！@樱
Mom, if we're cut off, it's the lightning
，如果我切嗔耍它的W
What?
什N？
Let's go rent a boat! I got 8 human heads in my room and I gotta go rent a boat!
我去租了一l船！我有8人的^在我的房g，我得去租了一l船！
Okay
好
Mrs. Pritshett?
夫人Pritshett？
Hi, this is Ernie Lipscomb, Charlie's friend from medical school
嗨，@是ernie利普斯科姆，查理的朋友尼tW院
Oh! Great! Great! The number of as many hotels as you can give me
哦！太好了！太好了！@底楹芏嗑频辏你可以o我
No, I know, it is, it is late
不，我知道，它是，它是晚
It's just that we've run into a little bit of a situation up here
只是，我遇到了一cc的情r在@e
All right, okay, the Mayan
好吧，好吧，雅
- That sounds great - No, no, no, relax, everything's fine
- @起聿诲e - 不，不，不，放，一切都很好
But I do need to get a hold of Charlie. Did he tell you what hotel he was staying at?
但我_需要得到持有查理。他有]有告V你什N是他所住酒店在哪e？
He didn't...
他]有 ...
Right, no, I know how sons can be
好了，不，我知道鹤被
- All right, and that's the last one, right? - Yeah, no, I'm good
- 所有的嗬，@是最後一，ΣΓ - 是啊，不，我很好
- School's a little crazy - Well, thank you
- W校是一有c狂 - 嗯，xx你
You know how that goes
你知道如何^m下去
You sure he's only going away for a week?
你_信他只是要x_一星期？
- He packed enough stuff here for a year - Charlie is a compulsive packer
- 他足虻|西在@eDM了一年 - 查理是一迫打包C
"Sleight of Mind" by Charlie Pritchett again
“斯R特的心”再次由查理普里奇特
He's writing a detective novel
他的商叫≌f
Yeah, it sounds like his autobiography
是啊，@起硐袼的自
It's a pun on sleight on hand and dim-witted. You know, a pun, play on words, get it?
@是一pPZ的花招在手，c心C智 你知道，一pPZ，文字[颍明白幔
No, no, no, relax. Everything's fine
不，不，不，放。一切都很好
No, I don't know we got midterms
不，我不知道我有期中考
I'll talk to you soon, Mrs. Pritshett gotta go, bye
我告V你一，夫人Pritshett得走了，再
I popped the last guy who tried to pun me, asshole. Get it?
我打_最後一砘镎lD一ZpP我，混蛋。明白了幔
Yeah, I get it too. Make some more calls
是啊，我得到它。作一些要求
You too, asshole
你也一樱混蛋
Charlie, this is none of my business, hopefully... but, let's review
查理，@是]有的，我的I眨希望...但是，我回
You've been pre-law, pre-architect, pre-vet, pre-med...
你已A先法，A建B，A核，A地中海...
- No, I'm in Med. - He's an intern
- 不，我在地中海。 - 他是一生
And now Laurie tells me you've been thinking about becoming a head-shrinker
F在，谘e告V我，你一直在思考如何成橐^，收sC
- Charlie - A... a what?
- 查理 - 答..一什N？
Shrink, headshrinker, psychoanalyst
收s，headshrinker，心理分析
Whatever you call an overpaid hand-holder these days
o你怎NQ呼一多付的手持有人@些天
Actually, sir, I was thinking about that... but I don't know what I'm doing anymore
其，主席先生，我想那 ...但我不知道我在做什N了
- I'm certainly aware of that - Dad, enough...
- 我然知道那 - 爸爸， ...
Annette?
涡闵？
Bear?
熊？
- Wooly, are we alone? - Yeah, we're alone, but where are you?
- 茸毛，我是一人幔 - 是啊，我很孤，但你在哪e？
Wooly!
毛茸茸！
- What are you doing there? - Wooly! Thank God Thank God you're alive!
- 什N是你在那e做什N？ - 毛茸茸！感x上帝，感x上帝，你活著！
Still alive? Of course I'm still alive
活著幔慨然，我活著
Where's Laurie? Not with him, oh my God! Not with that maniac!
哪e的谘e？不跟他在一起，哦，天哪！不c子！
Calm down and tell me what you're talking about
冷o下恚告V我你在f什N
What I'm talking about? Our daughter is dating a mass murderer
我f的是什N？我的女菏羌s的大屠
I went into his room to take a gift to put it in his bag
我走M他的房gбY物戆阉放在他的袋子
In his bag he's got body parts!
在他的袋子，他的身w部位了！
Senora Bennett, I sorry to scare you I was fixing the gutter
塞Z拉忍兀我Σ黄鹉悖我是唬修团潘
Dick, I am not crazy! I know what I saw!
迪克，我不是了！我知道我看到了！
- I believe you - No, you don't believe me
- 我相信你 - 不，你不相信我
Yes, I do believe you, but remember what the doctor said about your drinking
是的，我相信你，但住，t生f什N你喝酒
- I did not hallucinate - Bear
- 我]有a生幻X - 熊
I had the drink after I saw them Please, Wooly
我有後，我看到他，毛茸茸
Bear, what about the pills?
熊，怎N铀？
I saw you take them, you said yourself they made you woosy
我看你他，你自己f@你woosy
Right, but then what about the bag? Okay... where's the bag?
右，但後碓觞N拥陌？好了...哪淼陌幔
I don't know, but I was in his room when he unpacked
我不知道，但我在他的房gr，他解_
He unpacked right in front of me would a maniac do that?
他解_就在我面前的一子@N做？
Oh, no! Oh, no!
哦，不！哦，不！
No, no, no, no
不，不，不，不
It's not my room!
@不是我的房g！@不是我的房g！
It is my room, okay
@是我的房g，好
- Senor? - What?
- 塞{？ - 什N？
- We clean room
- 我Q室
- Room clean - Oh no!
- 房g乾Q - 哦，不！
Hola
HOLA的
- Oh! I am... - Paco?
- 噢！我是... - 帕？
No... I'm... blind... I'm blind I mean, I mean, you're blind...
第..我...盲人...我瞎了我 意思是，我的意思是，你是盲人...
I'm a guest and I forgot something
我是客人，我忘了什N
- Adios
- 阿迪W斯
- I draw the line on mass graves - Mass graves?
- 我f人坑 - |V墓？
You know, maybe we should just do individuals, seven of them, you know?
你知道，也S我做的人，其中含7，你知道幔
This reminds me of when I was a kid, I was thirteen years old
@使我想起我是孩子的r候，我十三q
Me and my friends used to rip the heads off Barbie dolls...
我和我的朋友都用欺_的後仰芭比娃娃...
and burry them in the mud in the backyard
和他在泥{埋在後院
- You used to rip the... - Hola, amigos
- 您用硭洪_ ... - HOLA的，戈斯
Find any buried treasures, gringos?
找到任何藏，gringos？
We have laws about these deserts
我的法律@些沙漠
They are environmentally protected now you know
他F在你知道保oh境
- Actually, no, we didn't know - Si, si
- 事上，不，我不知道 - 矽，矽
We got protected snakes, protected lizards
我得到了保o，蛇，蜥蜴保o
protected toads
保o蟾蜍
Are you familiar with the Mexican horny toad, chiquita?
你熟悉墨西哥角|蟾蜍，奇基塔？
- Oh, no - Oh, yeah!
- 噢，不 - 噢，是啊！
Mexican horny toad is a very special species
墨西哥角|蟾蜍是一非常特殊的物N
It's against the law to hurt a horny toad in any way...
@是`法的害角|蟾蜍以任何方式...
Oh! You just hurt a horny toad!
哦！你只蟾蜍害角|！
Laurie
谘e
Whoa, come on, amigos. Vamanos!
哇，戆桑戈斯。 Vamanos！
- Are you all right? - Yeah
- 你]事吧？ - 是啊
No, shit! They stole my car! Go get them!
不，死！他偷走了我的！他去！
- Senor - Dick is going to kill me
- 塞{ - 迪克⒘宋
I want you to stay here at your hotel
我希望你留在@旱木频
- Okay - You're much safer here
- 好吧 - 你在@e更安全
- Okay, thank you - Thank you
- 好吧，xx你 - xx你
Thank you, sir
xx您，主席先生
- Senor , you forgot your bag - Thank you, thank you, sir
- 塞{，你忘了你的包 - xx你，xx你，先生
Thank you, good night
xx你，晚安
Well, that went well
嗯，@很利
- Charlie! I got it! Fed Ex it! - What?
- 查理！我想到了！邦快f吧！ - 什N？
Fed Ex them to Steve!
邦快f公司o史蒂夫！
Fed Ex them? Laurie, we're in Mexico there is no Fed Ex
邦快f公司呢？谘e，我在墨西哥有]有邦快f
Well, then, Mex Ex them, I don't care the point is just ship them!
好吧，那N，墨西哥前他，我不在乎@一c，只是船他！
And just let Steve innocently open a package full of heads?
而只是史蒂夫天真，打_一包完整的^？
Of course not, we'll call him
然不是，我叫他
All right boys, I'd like to do this forever but...
好男孩，我想永h做下去，但...
I'm sorry, I don't know what else to do You know?
Σ黄穑我不知道自己能做些什N，你知道幔
I think it's time that I got rid of you two and moved along. Come on, come over here
我J檫@是一次我[了你沿著。戆桑到@
What? you, you can't just kill us We're trying, all right? We're trying...
什N？你，你不能只⒘宋，我 正在努力，好幔课正在努力...
Trying? What are you talking about? What does this look like the Special Olympics?
L？你在f些什N？@是什N幼拥奶厥W\？
I need the bag! Get over here
我需要的包！在@e@取
- Well, wait... - Trying, shit, get down!
- 嗯，等待... - L，狗屎，趴下！
Listen, we can call more people or...
著，我可以{用更多的人或...
Yes, we can help, man
是的，我可以提供椭，男子
I don't know what to do I can go through friends
我不知道怎Nk，我可以通^朋友去
Can I answer that? It might be Charlie, all right?
我可以回答@}？@可能是查理，好幔
Put it on speaker phone
把它b上免提
- Hello? - Steve
- j？ - 史蒂夫
- Oh God! - Oh, Charlie, thank God. Jesus!
- 哦，上帝！ - 哦，查理，感x上帝。耶d！
Listen to me, you asshole, you got my heads and I want them back, you understand?
我f，你混蛋，你有我的^，我想他回恚你明白幔
Who is this?
@是l？
Never mind who this is I want those heads!
]PS，我想@是l的^！
Jesus Christ! You're the guy from the airplane!
耶d基督！你是娘wC的砘铮
Charlie, listen, listen...
查理，著，著 ...
What does this look like, a family reunion?
@是什N幼樱一家庭F聚？
Steve? What are you doing to Steve?
史蒂夫？你在做什N是史蒂夫？
I'm killing him unless you shut up and listen to me! Where are you?
我⑺浪，除非你]嘴，我的！你在哪e？
I'm in Baja I'm six hours south of San Diego
我在巴哈我六小r}地哥以南
Listen to me. You meet me at the San Diego airport and bring all 8 heads with you
我f。你遇我在}地哥C觯⑺有8^c你
San Diego airport? I'm on vacation with my girlfriend's parents
}地哥C觯课液臀业呐友在度假的父母
Okay, okay, San Diego
好吧，好吧，}地哥
You make sure you're there by six o'clock if you ain't there, your buddies are history
你要_保你那e六c如果您是不存在，您的好友已成v史
- But what if I don't have all eight heads? - What?
- 但是，如果我]有全部八^？ - 什N？
- I lost one - You lost one?
- 我失去了一 - 你了幔
You lost one? How the hell could you lose one?
你了幔磕隳茉觞N就幔
The maid got it
得到它的女W
What do you mean a maid got it? How the hell did a maid...
你是什N意思女蛎靼琢幔康降资窃右女 ...
What, what do you mean? What, which one did you lose?
什N，你是什N意思？什N，你失去哪一？
I don't know!
我不知道！
Oh Jesus! I can't believe this shit! I can't believe this shit!
哦耶d！我直不敢相信@狗屎！我直不敢相信@狗屎！
Damn it!
死的！
What's happening?
@是怎N回事？
I don't know I don't think he's taking it too well
我不知道，我不J樗服用^好
Charlie, listen. The guy is serious he's not screwing around
查理，著。@砘锸乐氐模他的周]有搞砸
He's a psycho, all right? You gotta do what he says, all right?
他是一心理，好幔磕惚仨做什N，他f，好幔
- Are you there? - Yes, yes
- 你在幔 - 是的，是
Yeah, listen to this
是啊，@
All right, bring the rest and make sure you're there
好吧，把其N的，K_保你的存在
Remember what I'm telling you now you got it?
住我告V你，F在你明白了幔
- Got it. Before you hang up though... - What?
- 明白了。m然之前你先 ... - 什N？
If you hurt my friends you'll never get them
如果你害了我的朋友你永h不他
Charlie, what are you trying to do? Are you threatening me?
查理，你想质颤N？你在威{我幔
No, I'm just telling you a fact... and don't lose my book either
不，我只是告V你一事 ...K]有失去我的或
It's my only copy
@是我唯一的副本
Charlie
查理
All right! All right! All right! Forget the book, I'll be there
好吧！好吧！好吧！忘@本，我在那e
Yeah, you better
是啊，你最好
What's happening?
@是怎N回事？
We have to go back to San Diego
我必回到}地哥
San Diego? My dad will shit himself! What are we going to tell him?
}地哥？我的爸爸狗屎自己！什N是我要告V他？
What to you mean he forgot to turn in his lap report?
你f他怎N忘了把他腿上的蟾妫
- I know it sounds flaky and... - Flaky? It's ridiculous!
- 我知道@起碛悬c片詈... - 片睿克的荒！
You mean he came all the way to Mexico without turning in a report
你的意思是，他淼侥西哥，一路^也不回在一份蟾嬷
and for that we have to go home?
榇耍我要回家？
Mom is sick and anyway it's your fault
病了，反正@是你的e
My fault?
我的e？
He took your advice He's decided on something
他把你的意，他的Q定的|西
Well, he's decided that he'll never be a member of this family, that's for sure
那N，他的Q定，他⒂肋h不成檫@家庭的成T，@是肯定的
- We're leaving - How did he take it?
- 我要x_了 - 他是怎N考]的？
It's gonna have to fall under the category of blessing in disguise
@是要必凫额因得福
I'll make it up to him I'll give him a year of free analysis
我a上他，我o他一年的免M分析
- Cute. Here - What's this?
- 可邸Ｔ谶@e - @是什N？
It's a surprise for his birthday He likes his macho stuff
@是一@喜，他的生日，他喜g他的男子飧诺|西
Can you pack it in your bag? I don't want him to see it
你能在你的袋子包b好？我不想他看到它
Where exactly would you suggest I put it?
_切位置在哪e，你建h我把它？
- If we're going, let's get going - Right, dad
- 如果我走到哪e去，我去 - Γ爸爸
The shirt's for you. Get packing
@件r衫的你。掏b箱
And the macho statue with all the disgusting...
而c所有的大男子主x雕像f心 ...
Laundry
洗衣房
I didn't...
我]有 ...
Thank you
xx
Who's this guy? He might do
l是@砘铮克做
- Do for what? - Hugo
- 做什N？ - 雨果
Wait a minute
等一下
Are you telling us you're trying to find a look alike for the head Charlie lost?
你告V我，你D找到一L得很像的^部查理失去了什N？
Yeah. We got some time to kill before we go to the airport
是啊。我得到了一些rg⑺乐前，我去C
Oh, my God!
噢，我的上帝！
But these are college professors! You know, innocent people!
但是，@些都是大W教授！你知道，o辜的人民！
You can't just kill innocent people because they look like someone else
你不能只⒑o辜的人民，因樗看起硐e人
Let me tell you something, college boy nobody's innocent
我告V你，]有人大W男孩的o辜
Now, who is he?
F在，他是l？
He was my anatomy professor. He almost flunked me
他是我的解剖W教授。他缀醪患案裎
Good, here's your chance to get even with the prick. Get me his address
好，@e是你的C得到，即使有刺。o我他的地址
Wait a minute! I just thought of something!
等一下！我只是想到了什N！
- What? - Cryonics!
- 什N？ - 人w冷觯
- Cry- what?
- 哭，怎Nk？
Frozen bodies! This university has the biggest Cryonics Foundation
冷企w！@所大W碛凶畲蟮娜梭w冷龌金
in the country
在
So what?
等什N？
So it could save you a lot of troubles is so what!
因此，可以省你很多的麻┦侨绱耸颤N！
You go on a killing spree here, Big Sep's gonna hear about it
你去@e上大_⒔洌大九月的到@消息
When a couple of gangsters die nobody cares
一ΨD死亡的歹徒o人津
But you blow away professors Big Sep's gonna read about that
但你吹走教授大九月的x到@
Big Sep don't read
九月大不x
Still, this cryonics facility has hundreds of frozen bodies
管如此，@人w冷鲈O淅C有上百份
Why they got hundreds of frozen bodies?
槭颤N他得到了蛋冷C？
- I think for situations like this - Don't be a little smart ass
- 我X得像@拥那r - 不要一屁股小`通
They have them because people are hoping that in a couple hundred years...
他有他，因槿都希望，在一ΨD百年...
...maybe they can bring them back to life, clone them a healthy body
...也S他可以把他重新回到生活中，他一健康的身w克隆
- Are you jerking me around? - What?
- 你躲_我幔 - 什N？
Oh, my God, he just put welts and bruises over 90% of my body, now you're talking...
噢，我的上帝，他只把痕和青[超^ 90％的我的身w，F在你f ...
...about having me help you decapitate some professors. Would I be jerking you around?
...P於我湍厥子幸恍┙淌凇Ｎ躲_你身？
Calm down, tough guy. What are you trying to tell me?
冷o下恚硬h。你到底要告V我？
I'm trying to tell you that right across campus is a gold mine of heads
我想告V你，在校@鹊嗬是一金V的磁^
Heads R Us. Night of a Thousand Heads.
^玩具反斗城。夜一f^。
If I was a guy in desperate need of a head, as you are, I'd at least check it out
如果我是一人在^望需要一^，因槟闶牵我想至少z查出
Senor, I can't find your jeep anywhere
塞{，我找不到任何地方你的吉普
What do you mean you can't find it? It's red, rojo
你f你不能找到它？它的t色，_霍
Oh, my God. I forgot. We, we went for a drive last night
噢，我的上帝。我忘了。我，我去兜L昨晚
and... it got stolen
和...它被偷了
You forgot it was stolen?
你忘了@是被I用？
Well, we...
好吧，我 ...
This is ridiculous! How the hell are we going to get out of here?
@是荒的！到底如何我要x_@e？
It's not a problem, senor take a plane
@不是一}，先生乘坐wC
Oh, a plane! A plane! And where would we take a plane from?
哦，一架wC！一架wC！我在哪e乘坐wC的？
Here. Since you've been away, senor, this has become a very important city
在@e。既然你已x_，先生，@已成橐非常重要的城市
I mean we have built our own airport
我的意思是我已建立了自己的C
- A plane comes every day - Well, aren't we lucky?
- 一平面砻恳惶 - 好吧，我是不是幸\？
Now, that's a Hugo
F在，@是一雨果
- This one's good? - For Hugo Porter, unbelievable!
- @一好？ - 於雨果波特，真y以置信！
All right, we got a keeper!
好吧，我得到了一守TT！
- What was that? - Thawing it out
- 那是什N？ - 解龀
No way
不行
Good God! Look at that!
天哪！看看@！
Lassie, sit girl! Stay!
`犬R西，坐的女孩！e走！
Oh my God!
噢，我的上帝！
Guys! Ernie!
噢，我的上帝！伙！厄尼！
- What? - I'm not very comfortable, perhaps
- 什N？ - 我不是很舒服，也S
Why is that?
@是槭颤N？
We're messing with people's immortality here. It's murder!
我搞y人的不朽@e。@是\！
Technically, it's not murder, Steve because they're already dead
募夹g上v，@不是\，史蒂夫，因樗都已死了
No, these people, they believed in the freezing thing
不，@些人，他J樵鼋Y的事
All right, this is like grave robbing, grave robbing, or worse
好吧，@就像I墓，I墓，或者更糟
I don't see any graves. Do you see any graves?
我]有看到任何墓。你看不到任何墓？
There's gonna be two fresh ones, if you two don't start looking for heads, come on
有的是新r的，如果你z不_始找^，戆
All right
所有嗬
- Sir, I'm really sorry about the Jeep - It's open seating
- 主席先生，我真的很抱歉吉普 - 它的_放座位
Now you take these tickets and you check in the big stuff
F在你把@些T票和你的|西在大z查
We'll take the little stuff, and we'll go get the seats
我要抓住@小|西，我找一座位
Do you think you can handle that?
你J槟憧梢蕴理@}？
Yes, I really appreciate you...
是的，我真的很感x你...
Come on, Bear. Come here
戆桑熊。磉@e
God!
神！
Permiso, senor , do you have anything to declare?
Permiso，先生，你有什N要申幔
Any fruits, vegetables, native plants?
任何水果，蔬菜，原生植物？
Are you kidding?
你在_玩笑吧？
Sobrino! Sobrino!
Sobrino！ Sobrino！
Mira! Mira! Que es eso?
米拉！米拉！I ES的W洲南方天文台？
No se, mira como esta aqui
]有本身，米拉科莫埃斯塔aqui
Excuse me, could you handle me my bag, please?
Σ黄穑你能理我的包幔
- Un momento, senor - I don't have un momento!
- 合 momento，先生 - 我]有合 momento！
I have a plane-o to catch-o, got it?
我有一平面O碜汾s啊，明白了幔
- Machete? - No, sera una pistola?
- 砍刀？ - 不，色拉寺跫{ pistola？
Excuse me, it's right there, I can see it I'll just reach in and get it myself, okay?
Σ黄穑它的嗬在那e，我可以看到它我就_到K得到它自己，好幔
Senor... no. No, Senor!
塞{ ...]有。不，先生！
What? Is it dad?
什N？是爸爸幔
What?
什N？
They found two heads in Dad's carry-on
他lF，元首在父H的S身
Oh, no!
哦，不！
Put me down! Put me down!
放我下恚》盼蚁恚
Oh, my God!
噢，我的上帝！
Help me! Help me!
救救我！救救我！
- Decent, hold this one - Yeah, wait. Do you need a Helen?
- w面的，持此一 - 是啊，等待。你需要一海？
No, you can play with her when I leave Get over there
不，你可以跟她玩，我x_那e@取
- This guy do anything for you? - He's not bad either
- @砘镒鋈魏问虑幔 - 他的也不e
Could be a Stu
可能是斯D
- Yeah? - Yeah
- 是幔 - 是啊
We could beat him a little bit give him a few cuts
我可以打他一cco他一些削p
Random disfigurement
SC容
Yeah, definitely a Stu
是啊，^κ且斯D
Worth a try anyway. I'll take him and I'll take him
值得一呢。我他，我他
- Great, I'll wrap them up - What do you mean take? Huh?
- 太好了，我Y起 - 你是什N意思走？咦？
You know, for a future doctor you're a pretty stupid kid
你知道，於一未淼尼t生你是一很愚蠢的孩子
I mean take the heads
我的意思是走^
No, No
不，不
No, no way! You do it! This is your crazy idea, okay?
不，不行！你@幼觯∵@是你的狂的想法，好幔
It's my idea that you should do it
@是我的想法，你@幼
But, he's a neurologist, I'm only going into dermatology
但是，他的神科t，我⒅槠つw科
So don't screw up the skin
所以，不要搞砸了皮w
Now there's a pleasant sound
F在有一N耳的音
Mr. Escobedo, this is my mother, Annette, Charlie and Fran Bennett
埃斯科多先生，@是我的母H，涡闵，查理和弗m班尼特
Dad's mom. She flew down to help us out
爸爸的。她w落下椭我
Nona, this is Dad's Mexican lawyer
Z娜，@是爸爸的墨西哥律
- Delighted - Charmed
- 欣喜 - }女魔咒
Now, cut the crap and tell us what the hell's going on!
F在，U少f，告V我到底是什N回事！
Certainly
然
Miamigos, in your country
Miamigos，在F
you have what you call the good news and the bad news
你有你所^的好消息和南息
The good news is that Mr. Bennet underwent only very mild torture
好消息是，只接受班{特先生非常睾偷目嵝
- Jesus! - Oh my God!
- 耶d！ - 哦，我的上帝！
Shut up, you poodle. What's the bad news?
]嘴，你{子狗。什N是南息？
He confessed and was sentenced to death
他交待，被判死刑
- Oh my God! - That little weakling!
- 哦，我的上帝！ - 那小懦夫！
Oh, Mom!
哦，！
- Wait a minute. Don't get upset yet - Not get upset?
- 等待一分。不要生猓但 - ]有不高d？
Let the man speak, damn it!
男人f，死的！
There are remedies here. This is a civilized country
@e有a救措施。@是一文明的家
There's going to be a trial some sort of hearing
有的⑹且判某N力
Of course. When my partner arrives, we will formulate our strategy
然可以。我的夥伴到r，我制我的鹇
Until then, try to relax
在此之前，M量放
It's a beautiful day. Enjoy Mexico
@是一美好的一天。享受墨西哥
I can't belive it
我不敢相信它
Things get a little rough and he cracks
事情得有c粗糙，他裂p
- Nona, they tortured him - Oh, what?
- Z娜，他折磨他 - 哦，什N？
A little castor oil down his gullet?
一小蓖麻油了他的咽喉？
A little electricity on his dillywacker?
在他的一cc力 dillywacker？
Cat piss!
尿！
I am spent!
我花了！
Chopping off heads just takes it out of you
厝ヮ^只需要你出
Shit!
的！
Time to go, I got four heads I'm screwed
走了，我得到了四^，我Q
But you got a good start
但你有一良好的_端
I'm sure one of those heads in there will do for the one Charlie lost
我相信其中的一^在那e⒆鲆查理失去
I doubt it, the way my luck's running today, kid
我岩伤的幼樱我的\獾倪\行，今天的孩子
Let's take a second and take stock of where we are so far
我花一秒，K袢」善保我走了多h
Let me tell you something, kid, okay?
我告V你吧，孩子，好幔
Just so you know, I gotta kill the both of you
只要你知道，我要⑺滥z
So don't think by helping me it's gonna change that, all right?
所以不要以橥ㄟ^椭我碚f，@改@Nr，好幔
Yeah, I know, sure, I'm just saying that you're doing all right
是啊，我知道，然，我只是f你正在做的一切嗬
you might be better off than you think
你可能比你想的更好
Okay, but I'm just saying too I want you to know
好吧，但我只是f我想你也知道
Okay, let's see. I got a Hugo, a Marty, a so-so Stu, and a bad Frank
好吧，我砜纯础Ｎ矣杏旯，一R蒂，一RR虎虎斯D，母ヌm克
Right, and then at the morgue, you said something about Little Joey
α耍然後在太平g，你f了一些P於小桃
- Right - Okay
- 右 - 好
All right, so I got Little Joey, a Hugo, a Marty, and a bad Frank
好了，所以我就小桃粒一雨果，一R蒂，母ヌm克
- No, where's Stu? - I said Stu, so-so Stu
- 不，那e的斯D？ - 我f斯D，RR虎虎斯D
No, just a second ago, you said Little Joey
]有，只是一秒前，你f小桃
I know I said little Joey but I also said Stu
我知道我f什N，但我也f桃了D
But then where's Frank?
但是又在哪e的弗m克？
All right, let's start over You got a Hugo... a Little Joey...
好吧，我重新_始你有雨果...一小桃 ...
- ... a Frank... - Yeah
- ...坦率... - 是啊
- A bad Stu... - No... Frank... bad Frank
- 一乃D ... - 第..弗m克 ...母ヌm克
That's what I said
@就是我f的
No, you didn't, you said bad Stu, Stu was just so-so
不，你]有，你f乃D，斯D只是RR虎虎
No, sir, I said a so-so Stu You did not. You said bad Stu
不，先生，我fRR虎虎斯D你]有。你f不好斯D
Yes, I said. Everyone heard
是的，我f。每人都^
I said so-so Stu
我fRR虎虎斯D
You said bad Stu! I know their names and you don't
你f不好斯D！我知道他的名字，你不
Will you two stop it! Goddamnit!
你晌蛔∈郑 Goddamnit！
These are not baseball cards we're talking about here, all right?
@些都不是棒球卡，我正在@e，好幔
These are heads, human beings' heads
@是^，人的^
Where were we?
我f到哪了？
- I said we have a Hugo - Yes
- 我f，我有一雨果 - 是
Ho, ho, wait a minute, just a sec.
嗬，嗬，等待一分，只是酌腌。
I can't believe I didn't notice this before
我o法相信我]有注意到@之前
What?
什N？
With some black hair and a busted nose, this kid makes a decent Frank
S著一些黑^，打掉的鼻子，@小子使一w面的弗m克
- What? - Yeah
- 什N？ - 是啊
I mean I know you're a little young, but with that stubble
我是f我知道你是一小青年，但是c@茬
- a couple of missing teeth - But you have a Frank
- 一ΨD缺牙 - 但你必坦\
I got a bad Frank, you make a better one
我有一牡母ヌm克，你犯了一更好的
But you don't even know if you need a Frank!
但你甚至不知道你是否需要坦\！
- I might - Please no, please, no
- 我可能 - 不，不
Listen, please, no, listen I don't want any trouble
著，，不，著，我不想有任何麻
Look, I fly, I fly
你看，我w，我w
- What are you? A fairy? - No, no, he has a pilot's license
- 你是什N？一位仙女？ - 不，不，他有一w行T陶
You don't wanna fly commercial airlines with all these heads
你不想要w商I航空公司所有@些^
That's how you got in this whole mess. He can fly us. It's smarter
@就是你如何在@整一F糟。他能w我。它的明
I fly
我w
All right, grab all those heads. Just leave the top one
好吧，抓住那些^。x_前一
Why?
槭颤N呢？
Because the top one doesn't look like anybody and Big Sep will never buy it
因轫右徊幌袢魏稳耍大九月⒉辉儋I它
Wait just a minute! I sawed this off and you re not even gonna use it?
等待一分！本人@一P，你甚至不打算重新使用它？
- Steve, chill - No, you chill
- 史蒂夫，寒 - 不，你冷
It s not fair. I spent a lot of time on this head
@不公平。我花了很多rg在@^
Don't you think that you could've at least told me this before I cut it off?
y道你不J槟憧赡芤呀至少告V我，@之前，我把它割下恚
I saw that coming
我看到未
- Don't fuck with a guy looking for heads - Good advice
- 不要他的跟男人找^ - 好建h
Now take all the heads and let's go, okay?
F在所有的首I，我走，好幔
- Big Sep, it's Benny - Where the hell are my heads?
- 大9月，它的本尼 - 到底哪e是我的^？
I just talked to Tommy a while ago. He'll be there tomorrow
我^米在不久前。明天他在那e
First it was two weeks ago, then three days ago
首先，它是星期前，然後三天前
I gave them to Tommy. It's Tommy's deal now
我把它交o米。@是Tommy的fhF在
Don't you talk to me about Tommy. I trust Tommy
你不跟我f米。我相信米
This is your job
@是你的工作
Big Sep, what are we talking about here
大月，什N是我@e所f的
Heads! It's not like they got any value on the open market
^！@K不是f他有任何在公_市錾系r值
It's not like we re talking diamonds here
它不象我重新在@e石
now that's what's bothering me Ben
F在，@是什N困_著我本
A guy pays 80 grand and doesn't see proof ...
一砘镏Ц80大，K]有看到C ...
He starts thinking maybe, just maybe he's been double-crossed, you know what I mean?
他_始想，也S，只是也S，他一直p，你知道我是什N意思？
Big Sep, I swear on the soul of my dead mother, I off them myself
大九月，我l誓我的`魂，死去的母H，我^他自己
me, and Rico, I give you my word!
我，波多黎各，我o你我的！
Your word ain't what I paid you 80 fucking grand for, Ben
你的是不是我付你80他的盛大，本
I paid you 80 fucking grand to see their fucking heads
我付你80他的他的隆重看到自己的^
Now you bring me their heads
F在你把我的^
Bennie! Bennie, Bennie, come in here, hurry up!
尼！本尼，尼，淼竭@e，快c！
Bennie, you re not gonna believe this! look, look at this!
本尼，你再不相信的！看，看@！
- My God! That's Hugo! - That s Hugo and Stu, I mean...
- 我的上帝！@是雨果！ - 只是@幼拥挠旯和斯D，我的意思是...
didn't I tell you he'd screw up, Bennie, didn't I tell you?
我]有告V你他搞砸了，本尼，我]告V你幔
- This ain' t good - What the hell's Big Sep gonna say, Bennie
- @艾因'好 - 你到底的大九月f，尼
Shut up!
]嘴！
Ernie Lipscomb, Please pick up a courtesy phone
厄尼利普斯科姆，拿起Y貌
This is Ernie Lipscomb
@是厄尼利普斯科姆
Ernie, it's Charlie. Let me talk to him
厄尼，它的查理。我跟他
- Sure. It's for you - Yeah?
- 然。@δ - 是幔
Hi, it s Charlie, l... I lost two more heads
嗨，查理，湖..我失去了^
What? how could you lose two more heads?
什N？你怎N能失去^？
- The police got them - How could the police get them?
- 警察抓住他了 - 警察怎N能得到呢？
The one I lost earlier, I got it back
才我失去了一，我回砹
What are you looking at?
你在看什N？
He's talking about potheads
他在 potheads
We re de-programmers with marijuana anonymous
我重新去程序Tc大麻匿名
He hates to lose a client
他失去一客舳
Listen to me, you little incompetent piece of shit! Where are you exactly?
我f，你@小不Q的一K狗屎！你到底是哪e？
The La Purisima Hotel
酒店的拉珀西R
Don't move. Don't leave your room for anything. I coming down there
不要印２灰x_你的房ge任何|西。N下磉有
If there s any more heads missing by the time I get there
如果有那更多的元首失踪的r候我到那e
I'm gonna replace them with your family and your friends, you hear me, huh?
我要取代它c你的家人和你的朋友，你到我幔
He really cares, and that's what makes him the best
他真正P心，而@正是使他成樽詈玫
What?
什N？
I'm thinking that once he gets these away from us your dad's a goner
我在想，一旦他得到@些x我你爸爸是一完了
We gotta move
我得
I, I saw a place just outside of here, we gotta check into another hotel, come on, get up!
我，我看到了外面的一地方在@e， 得z查到另一家酒店，戆桑站起恚
Uhm, I'll take these I had nowhere else to put them
嗯，我就I@些，我]有e的地方可把它
I'll take these to the American border, I'll give them to the police
我I@些γ境，我向他向警察
I'll rent a car I'll drive all night
我要租一v，我_送整夜
- What am I gonna tell my mother? - Tell her anything
- 那我要告V我的母H？ - 告V她做任何事
Tell her we had a fight, tell her I called you fat
告V她我吵了一架，告V她我叫你胖
It doesn't matter what she thinks the important thing is to save your dad
@K不重要，她J樽钪匾的是拯救你的爸爸
I'm not fat
我不胖
Look Laurie, maybe your dad was right about me
谘e看，也S你爸爸ξ沂钦_的
Maybe, I'm a total nimrod who can't follow through on anything
也S，我不能按照尼姆_德l通^什N
But I got him into this
但我他到@
I promise you, I'm gonna get him out
我答你，我一定他出
Get your hands off her Maniac!
您的p手把她的狂！
Hold on!
猿郑
You may want me to think I'm crazy but I'm not crazy and I'm not stupid
你可能要我X得我了，但我不是了，我不傻
you had those heads hidden in your room, and then you pinned them on my Dick
你有那些^藏在你的房g，然後他ξ壹挠璧峡
Mom, what are you saying?
，你f什N？
I'm calling the police on him, I'm gonna do it right now
我打恚警方在他身上，我要F在就做
- No
- 不
Mom, calling the police is a bad idea. No, no
，叫警察是一闹饕狻２唬不
Laurie, I love you. Take your hand off the phone you, back off, I know exactly what I am doing
谘e，我勰恪恐你的手你放下 ，回的r候，我_切地知道我在做什N
No, you, you're not thinking clearly
不，你，你]有想清楚
I am thinking perfectly. I know exactly what I am doing. I told you to back off!
我的想法很好。我_切地知道我在做什N。我叫你回砹耍
Operator? No, I wasn't yelling at you. Could you get me the police please?
算？不，我不是喊你。你能不能臀野丫察幔
Oh yes, operator, I need you to get the police for me, policia?
哦，是的，I者，我要你Ь察ξ碚f，policia？
Si, si, si, I'm trying to reach the police, the policia, si, gracias...
矽，矽，矽，我D到警察，policia，矽，格拉西斯 ...
Yes, Si, Si!
是的，矽，矽！
Yes, of course, I'll hold, I'm happy to hold
是的，然，我猿窒氯ィ我很高de行
For Christ s sake, keep it down!
因基督的故，小c！
Yes, oh, hello, police, yes, I have...
是的，哦，你好，警察，是的，我有...
Charlie, hurry! Go!
查理，快c！走！
- I need to rent a car - Sure, that's no problem
- 我需要租一v - 然，@不是什N}
We got chevys, jeep, chevys...
我得到了雪佛R，吉普，雪佛R ...
Hey, that looks like our jeep
嘿，@好像我的吉普
Well, uh, there's a lot of jeeps, you know, senor
嗯，有很多的吉普，你知道，先生
With this magazine in them? I don't think so. This jeep was stolen from us
有了@本sI的呢？我不J槿绱恕＿@吉普奈被偷走
I don't know, senor a lot of people read magazines
我不知道，先生很多人看sI
On seizures? You gotta be kidding me!
P於@？你必是在_玩笑吧！
You really like that magazine, huh? I'll tell you what I'm gonna do
你真的很喜g那本sI，是吧？我告V你我怎Nk
You rent this jeep, I'm gonna throw in magazine for Nada
你租@吉普，我扔在sI的{_
Unbelievable!
y以置信！
Excuse me. where can we rent a car? Thanks!
Σ黄稹Ｎ在哪e可以租到？xx！
All right, make sure it has A.C Hold on, champ. Thanks
好吧，_保它具有交流猿窒氯ィ冠。xx
Are you telling me I just passed out?
你告V我，我通^了幔
Come on, drink up, you're a little dehydrated
戆桑喝起恚你是一有c水
- I'm gonna get us packed - My butt's staying right here
- 我得到我的行b - 我的屁股的呆在家e
Why? I hear the Tropicana s wonderful
槭颤N呢？我到特_皮卡{奇妙
It's a waste of money, honey! Give me the two c's, a cot and a crapper, I'm set
@是一N浪MX，H鄣模〗o我的 C的，一小床和一R斯克拉普，我O置
But...
但是...
Laurie, Charlie, it's Ernie
谘e，查理，它的厄尼
- Jesus! - Who the hell is Ernie?
- 耶d！ - 到底是l厄尼？
- Nobody, grandma - Well, he sure as hell seems to know you
- ]有人，奶奶 - 嗯，他肯定是地z，似乎知道你
- No, grandma - Is this some guy you're boffing on the side?
- 不，奶奶 - @是一你正在boffing的一面呢？
- Grandma! - What the hell are you doing?
- 奶奶！ - 你到底在质颤N？
- Where's Charlie? - Who are you?
- 在哪e的查理？ - 你是l？
I asked you a question where the fuck is Charlie?
我你一}所在他的是查理？
And I asked you a question, who the fuck are you?
我你一}，l他的是你幔
Now that we're in this frigging La Purisima, what do we do now?
F在，我在@死拉珀西R，我怎Nk呢？
We find a cop station and we get our heads
我lF一警察站，我把自己的^
All right
所有嗬
Benny! Look! It's him! It's Tommy!
本尼！瞧！@是他！@是米！
What the hell do you think he's doing? Do you think he got the heads back already?
什N是地z，你J樗做的？你J樗得到了X袋後面了幔
I don't know, but why don't we follow him? Come no!
我不知道，但槭颤N我不跟他走？戆桑不！
Where the hell is he going?
他到底是在哪e去？
Keep following him
^m遵循他
I told Charlie to stay put
我告V查理留在原地
I told that son-of-bitch to stay put
我告V鹤拥模母狗留在原地
So who are you? God? Why the hell should he listen to you?
所以，你是l？上帝？他嵋你的？
Oh! I am so groggy! Do you mind if I lie down in the back?
哦！我@N糊里糊T的！你介意我躺下在後面？
I don't give a shit what you do lady, just keep quiet
我不o你做什N的狗屁的女士，保持沉默
Watch your language
注意你的Z言
Ow! Fern, stop it! Ugh!
噢！蕨菜，住手！唉！
Oh! My God!
哦！我的上帝！
Another head? Oh! My God!
另一^？哦！我的上帝！
Lady, lady, shut up!
夫人，女士，]嘴！
I can't stand it! I'm losing my mind! Everywhere I look are heads!
我受不了了！我失去我的心！我到都看的^！
Shut up, lady! Jesus Christ!
]嘴，小姐！耶d基督！
You're not the only person on this planet with problems
你不是唯一的人在@星球上有}
Shut it!
P]它！
Jesus! What a head case!
耶d！什N^案！
Is that supposed to be a joke? Killer humour!
是，是一笑幔⑹钟哪！
looks like this guy I dated in High School
@砘锟雌硐裎壹s高中
Hugo Porto
雨果波D
Hey, I think we're gonna pull over because we need some gas soon
嘿，我想我拉^恚因槲需要一些怏w很快
- Keep fucking driving - Didn't I tell you to watch your language?
- 保持他的{ - 我不是告V你要注意你的Z言？
What are you doing? Where are you going?
你在质颤N？你要去哪e？
Get your hands off me, you goon! Don't fuck with me!
您的p手放_我，你呆子！e他的跟我恚
Grandma!
奶奶！
- My money says he ain't got the head - Mine, too
- 我的Xf，他]有得到你的^ - 我的，太
Man, how could you do that?
男人，你怎N能@幼瞿兀
- How could I what? - Throw her off the cliff?
- 我怎N能什N？ - 把她已拢
A man can only take so much, Kid
一人只能@N多，和
Oh! My God! I can't believe it!
哦！我的上帝！我不能相信！
I can't believe he...
我不能相信他...
- I thought the old battle-ax would never die! - Mom!
- 我以槔香X永h不死！ - ！
What do you wanna do now?
你F在要做？
Keep following him, but I don't like the smell of this
^m遵循著他，但我不喜g@味道
- Well, well, well, if it isn't our old amingo - Oh! No! not again!
- 嗯，好，好，如果不是我的老amingo - 噢！不！不吧！
Isn't once enough, huh? Can't you give a guy a break?
不是一次不颍是吧？你能不能o一人休息？
From one human being to another
囊人到另一
That's, that's very moving, gringo
@是，@是非常感人，格里戈
But the real question is, are we gonna cut off your conjones? Or live them on?
但真正的}是，我怎N剪了你的conjones？或住他呢？
You don't have to do this, come on guys, you can't kill me, can't we flip for it
您]有@幼觯你戆桑你⒉涣宋遥我不能樗翻D
You think you should kill me, flip for it?
你J槟⒘宋遥翻D呢？
- What? - A coin, you know?
- 什N？ - 一枚硬牛你知道幔
Flip a coin, I win you let me go, you win you mangle me
硬牛我A了，你我走，你A了我，你裂
you're a crazy man, gringo
你是一狂的人，格里戈
- Call it - Heads
- Q之 - ^
Oh, you sure? you don't even wanna you sure you don't wanna think about it?
哦，你_定幔磕闵踔敛幌Ｍ你真的不想去想它？
I've never been more sure of anything in my life
我]有去^更_信我生命中的任何|西
Juan! Don't take the keys! Don't take the keys!
胡安！不要把匙！不要把匙！
Oh, God!
哦，上帝！
Oh, this has not been a very good vacation
哦，@不是一很快返募倨
Hello? Hello!
j？您好！
Who's there?
l在那海
Stop! Stop!
住手！住手！
- Not your kind of music - I hate that shit
- 而不是你N的音 - 我恨那些歌
Are you talking to me?
你在跟我f幔
I said, are you talking to me?
我f，你跟我f幔
I don't know who you're talking to
我不知道你在和lf
- I'm the only one here - Shut the fuck up!
- 我是唯一一在@e - P]他的了！
- Are you talking to me? - Yeah, I'm talking to you, shut up!
- 你跟我f？ - 是啊，我跟你f，]嘴！
Shut up... Screwball!
]嘴 ...怪僻！
- What's that? - What's what?
- 那是什N？ - 什N是什N？
Stop! stop!
住手！停！
Oh! No!
哦！不！
Whoa, hold on now! Hold on, hold on, just okay, okay
哇，等一等吧！猿肿。猿肿。好，好
Hey, come here, stop
嘿，^恚停
okay, don't shoot! Don't shoot!
好了，不要_！不要_！
I thought I told you to stay put?
我想我告V你留下恚
Where's my heads? Where's my heads?
哪e是我的^？哪e是我的^？
They're in the jeep They're in the coolers
他在他的吉普在冷s器
- Good - But I lost another one
- 良好的 - 但是我失去了一又一
What?
什N？
Here, coyote
在@e，郊狼
- What's he doing? - The kid ain't dead, that's for sure
- 什N是他在质颤N？ - @孩子]有死，@是肯定的
Here coyote!
在@e，郊狼！
- Shut! - What?
- ]嘴！ - 什N？
- Shut up! - What? What is it?
- 什N？是什N呢？
I'm dead, shit, I'm dead
我死了，的，我死了
Who, uh, whoever they are, it doesn't look like they're coming after us
l，嗯，o他是l，它看起K不像他砹酸幔我
Not yet. Just the fact that they're here means I'm dead though
]有。事上，他只是在@e表示我已死了，m然
When? As soon as I give you the heads?
什Nr候？我o你的首幔
Or as soon as I get them across to the States
或者，我他到美各地
Knowing them, they're gonna let me take that risk too
了解他，他袢∵@一LU，我太
Who are the heads anyway?
l是^呢？
What? Non of your business What the hell do you care?
什N？不P你的什N你到底在乎幔
You spend your vacation with a bunch of heads, you kind of want to know
你的假期你花了一堆^，你想知道N
You think about their hopes and their dreams
你想想他的希望和粝
Their lives cut short
他的生活s短
Hopes? Dreams? Those bums?
希望？粝耄窟@些？
You have to feel something!
你有什N感X！
You don't just kill eight people and not feel anything!
你不⒘税巳烁杏X不到什N！
It don't really matter, but let's just set the record straight, okay?
@其K不重要，但是我只O置打抱不平，好幔
First of all, I didn't whack them, those guys did
首先，我]有重羲，那些人做
Second, Mister Phi Beta Craphead
二，先生披塔 Craphead
If I hadn't fucked up, I'd be retiring after this
如果我]有性交了，我在@之後退休
Hey! Hey! look! look!
嘿！嘿！瞧！瞧！
What is he doing? It looks like he's chasing after a dog?
他在做什N？看起硭的狗追逐？
- What if we could help each other out here? - Impossible
- 如果我能互相椭幔 - 不可能
Why?
槭颤N呢？
Because you're stupid besides I'm not gonna take the chance of going across that border
因槟闶怯薮赖模除了我不抓住@C走出去跨越@l界
Well, if you know it all then how come you're in this mess to begin with?
好吧，如果你知道@一切那N你怎N_始在@子呢？
Because of bad luck
因檫\獠缓
It's not my fault that the bag was to big to go in carry-on
@不是我的e，是大袋子走在S身yУ
There was a gift shop right next to the gate
有一家Y品店T口旁
Didn't you ever think of taking two bags?
y道你不X得服用杉行李？
Oh! Shit!
哦！的！
So I'll repeat the question, what if there's where a way we could help each other out?
因此，我重}的}，如果有一N方法，我可以在互相椭幔
What way?
什Nk法？
I'm not into mass murder if I'm not getting paid for it
我]有M入大模\，如果我]@得我付了
But I'm warning you, anybody gets in my way is dead
但我警告你，任何人在我的方式得到死
- Thank you again for getting rid of fern - Mom!
- 再次感x您[蕨 - ！
The going rate five thousand dollars, but you can owe me lady
F行利率五千美元，但你欠我的夫人能
Where's he going?
在哪e，他要去哪e？
I don't know, Do I look a mind reader? Let's go, come on
我不知道，y道我看的心思？走吧，走吧
So now what do we do? Drive to the border?
所以，F在我怎Nk？_到境？
Hello no! We gotta get those heads back and save your dad
你好，不！我得那些X袋後面，省你的爸爸
Hey! Come back here! I'll kick your ass!
嘿！回恚∥揖吞吣愕钠ü桑
- Come on Bennie let's take him now - I expect that's exactly what he wants
- 戆赡嶙我他F在 - 我期望@正是他想要的|西
Uh, let's see, how lucky
嗯，我看看，多N幸\
We got here. Ah, we got Marty
我淼竭@e。啊，我得到了R蒂
Ah, we got Benito
啊，我有尼托
Little Joey
小桃
What is he doing?
他在做什N？
I don't know, it s like he's teasing us wait a minute it's caught on my neck!
我不知道，@就像他的蚺我等待一分的抓住我的脖子！
Ouch, Jamal, you wanna bite, huh?
哎眩ZR，你要咬，是吧？
Jamal! Jamal!
ZR！ZR！
Let's see, what do I need?
我看看，需要什N？
I need a Stu, a Frank and a Hugo
我需要一斯D，坦\和雨果
There's a Hugo
有一雨果
- Who is it? - It looks like Stu or Hugo
- 是l？ - 它看起硐袼D或雨果
Frankie you suck... but you're gonna have to do, buddy
弗m基你@傻...但你得做，伙
How many has he got now?
他碛卸嗌倌兀
He's got one, two seven, eight .
他有一，七，八。
- He's got all eight heads - I'm gonna make him the ninth head
- 他得到了所有八^ - 我湎蛩提出的第九妙^
And you, you I definitely don't need
而你，你，我肯定不需要
what a bunch of douchebags!
什N是一束douchebags！
Lost dreams! What a crock!
失落的粝耄∈颤N一缸！
This coyote won't be doing anymore running away
@狼不做了逃跑
I got him trained!
我他！
That is disgusting I can't leave it outside for the coyotes
@是令人旱模我不能x_它外出的郊狼
Everybody be still, this is our last match
每人是寂o的，@是我的最後一霰荣
Good work Steve, you asshole!
良好的工作史蒂夫，你混蛋！
That's it, we're just gonna have to wait till dawn
就@樱我只是要等到天亮
Steve, shut up!
史蒂夫，]嘴！
Heads up! Stop ahead!
心！停止前M！
Anybody need to use the head!
任何人都需要使用的^！
Steve, shut up and go to sleep
史蒂夫，]嘴，睡X去
Oh, don't let it go to your head whoa, whoa, whoa, you're way ahead of me
哦，不要他走了你的^哇，哇，哇，你在我前面的方法
Steve!
史蒂夫！
Hey, don't bite my head off, all right?
嘿，e咬我的^了，好幔
- That's it, I m sleeping outside guys - Me too
- 就是@樱我樗在外面砘 - 我也是
Steve! Get a grip, go to sleep
史蒂夫！@取抓地力，去睡X
Or what, huh? You'll have my head?
是什N，是吧？有我的^？
Enough!
蛄耍
Mr. Hitman
⑹窒壬
I'm so alone
我很孤
Ain't got no body to call my own
]有的身w是凫段业
Ain't got no legs for walking all over
]有的p腿走路都超^
Can't hold my liquor so I gotta stay sober
不能引起我的酒，所以我要保持清醒
Mr. hitman, give me a break
⑹窒壬，o我一突破
Tell Mr. Pizza that I ain't no steak
比_先生告V我，是不是]有牛排
Please put on your magic sheen
把你的魔法光
Mr. Hitman bring me a dream
⑹窒壬o我一
Jesus!
耶d！
- Bennie! Wake up! He's up! He's up! - I'm up! I'm up! Relax!
- 尼！醒醒吧！他的了！他的了！ - 我了！我起床！放！
Damn it! This always works on the Camaro
死的！@始K工程卡洛
- You can do it - I Know. All right!
- 您可以做到@一c - 我知道。好吧！
Can I get some breakfast here?
我可以在@e得到一些早餐？
Si, Senior, please, sit anywhere you like
四，高，坐在您想要的位置
- Bennie, what the hell is he doing? - I don't know, let's go find out, shall we?
- 本尼，他到底是什N做的？ - 我不知道，我去看看，好幔
- Coffee, Senor? - Uh, yeah, good
- 咖啡，先生？ - 嗯，好的，
- Juice? - Sure
- 果汁？ - 然
Wow, look at this surprise!
哇，看看@意外的@喜！
Bennie, Rico, you boys decide to take a vacation?
本尼，波多黎各，您男孩Q定去度假？
Yeah, Tommy, you know we never seen Mexico
是啊，米，你知道我]有^墨西哥
We figured this is a good time to check it out
我估@是一很好的rgz查出
Good, good... it's nice down here
好，好...真的很高d到@e
l know you re waiting for me to cross over to the States
升知道你再等我到^的家
But I gotta tell you now, when I do
但是我要告V你，我@幼
You'll get that bag over my dead body
你拿到了我的企w袋
Funny. We was thinking exact same thing, huh, Rico?
有趣的。我的想法完全一拥|西，呵呵，波多黎各？
That's his Van
@是他的
The guy with the van, where is he?
@砘锏狞I包，他在哪海
Uh, he's in the hotel, Senior
嗯，他在酒店，高
You're not going in there after him , are you?
你不在那e後，他，是幔
We need those heads, yes, I'm going in there
我需要@些元首，是的，我在那e
l can't believe you're actually doing this
升不能相信你真的@幼
Give me your guns
o我你的
Jesus! Charlie, where'd you get that?
耶d！查理，你哪号淼模
- It looks like mine - It was yours
- 它看起硐裎业 - @是你的
You dropped it in the dessert, now it's mine
你掉了它在沙漠，F在是我的
now both of you, put your guns on the table
F在o你，把你的在桌上
Or I'm gonna blow your heads off
不然我就把你的X袋吹
Right now!
F在！
Laurie, get the guns
谘e，得到了
Ernie, get the duffel bag
厄尼，得到行李袋
- Wait a minute! - Easy, kids
- 等一下！ - 危孩子
You don't wanna mess with these guys
你不想招惹@些砘
He's right, Charlie, what do you want those heads for anyway?
他是Φ模查理，你怎N想的首X呢？
He's gonna take them to the border, and turn in, right, Charlie?
他要他到境，K打_，右I，查理？
- You'll be a hero with her old man - Something like that
- 你成橐英雄c她的老男人 - 似的|西
Forget about it, you do that and Big Sep kills us all
算了吧，你@幼觯大九月⑺牢所有人
Fuck Big Sep!
他的大九月！
- Mrs. Bennett, Senor Prit-Shit - Paco
- 忍靥太，先生Prit狗屎 - 帕
We're F.B.l! He's the Unibell man
我 FBL的！他是Unibell人
Senora Bennett?
塞Z拉忍幔
Back off
後退
Come on, Laurie, drive faster
戆桑谘e，悠魉俣雀快
What have you done? Laurie, why do you have guns?
你做了什N？谘e，你槭颤N有？
What... what...
什N ...什N ...
Senor Pritchit, senor Bennett, what's happening? What's this all about?
塞{ Pritchit，先生本忍兀@是怎N回事？@是什N回事？
It's about heads
@是P於^
- Steve, leave him alone - Why does she have guns?
- 史蒂夫，他自x_ - 她槭颤N有？
Look! See? Heads ! All right?
瞧！看到了幔款^！好吧？
I know, but it's okay, Paco, Paco
我知道，但是]PS，柏高，柏高
I told you it wasn't recyclable
我告V你@是不能回收利用
Paco, it's okay, Paco
柏高，@]PS，帕
Charlie, what are we gonna do? Charlie?
查理，我怎Nk？查理？
- What are you doing? - Ernie, give me the duffel bag
- 你在质颤N？ - 厄尼，o我的行李袋
Everybody stay in the car!
每人都留在上！
Steve, stay in the car!
史蒂夫，留在上！
Move, please! Move!
移樱！移樱
Hola! Hola!
你好！你好！
I have something to declare!
我有事要宣布！
His mistake, he doesn't have anything
他的e`，他K]有什N
Arrest them! Arrest them!
逮捕他！逮捕他！
That's his bag! Arrest them
@是他的包！逮捕他
All right, everybody freeze!
好，大家不S樱
Don't do anything stupid and nothing stupid will happen
不要做任何愚蠢，l生什N愚蠢的
- Get to the plane, Rico - Oh! Shit!
- @取到平面，波多黎各 - 噢！的！
No need to be excited!
不需要@蛹樱
Charlie!
查理！
We're just getting in the plane and fly away, bye-bye, have a nice day
我在wC上，又w走了，再，再，有一愉快的一天
Arrest them!
逮捕他！
Drop your guns or I'm gonna shoot him
放下，不然我就把他拍
- Move in, goddamnit! - No!
- 移樱goddamnit！ - 不！
Charlie! No!
查理！不！
Arrest them! Check their bag! Open their bag!
逮捕他！z查他的包！打_他的包！
There's a human head in the bag!
有一人的^部在袋子！
The man you arrested yesterday is in jail
名男子被捕，昨天是你在Oze
for the murders these guys committed
於@些人犯下了\
He father is innocent
他的父H是o辜的
These are the guys who did it
@些砘锸钦l做的
Right there!
就在那海
Wait a minute! That's not ours!
等一下！@不是我的！
- You arrested us for the wrong head! - Rico
- 你逮捕了我殄e`的^！ - 波多黎各
- Our heads are not here! - Shut up!
- 我的^X是不是在@e！ - ]嘴！
- Where are our heads, asshole? - Shut up, Rico
- 在哪e是我的^，混蛋？ - ]嘴，波多黎各
Al suelo!
X suelo！
You knew it? You planned it?
你知道幔磕愕挠呢？
- You got a future, kid! - Thanks
- 你有一未恚孩子！ - xx
"Slight of Bag by Charlie Pritchett"
“p微的袋由Charlie普里奇特”
Show me the law about bringing a head out of the country
o我砹朔律P於^走出T
It ain't a fruit, it ain't a vegetable it ain't a native plant, goddamnit!
@是不是一N水果，它不是一N蔬菜它 是一原生植物，goddamnit！
Alto! Alto!
W拓！W拓！
You can't have it! It's mine!
你不能有它！@是我的！
I spent a lot of time on this head It's my best friend!
我花了很多rg在@^，@是我最好的朋友！